http://youtu.be/ahTNBXBI-rA
phungdo_vgu http://youtu.be/ahTNBXBI-rA
RAMESH YERRABALLI: Hi, I'm Ramesh Yerraballi, a senior lecturer here at
Chào, tôi là RAMESH YERRABALLI, giảng viên ở
the University of Texas at Austin.
trường ĐH Texas tại Austin.
I have dual appointments from the Department of Electrical and Computer
Tôi làm việc ở hai nơi Khoa Điện - Kĩ Thuật Máy Tính
Engineering and Biomedical Engineering.
và Kĩ thuật Y Sinh.
I've been a researcher and a teacher for the past 20 years.
Tôi vừa nghiên cứu vừa giảng dạy đã hơn 20 năm nay.
My research interests are in real time systems, multimedia communications,
Hướng nghiên cứu tập trung: hệ thống thời gian thực, truyền thông đa phương tiện,
and operating system security.
và bảo mật hệ điều hành.
As a teacher, I've been teaching courses in computer
Là giảng viên, thì tôi đang dạy vài môn khoa học máy tính
science off all subjects.
trong tất cả các môn.
What I've been doing more recently is teaching embedded systems, programming
Gần đây tôi đang giảng về Hệ thống Nhúng, lập trình
at all levels, and statistics and probability.
ở mọi cấp, thống kê và xác suất.
Jon, my colleague, may have written the book on embedded systems, by I
Jon, đồng nghiệp của tôi, đã biên soạn giáo trình hệ thống nhúng, tôi
make him look good when I teach from it.
làm anh ấy cảm thấy vui khi lấy sách anh ấy giảng dạy.
I love teaching, but what I like more than teaching is building things.
Tôi thích giảng, nhưng tôi thích làm cái gì đấy hơn là giảng dạy.
And I hope to share my passion for building and teaching
Hi vọng tôi có thể lan tỏa niềm đam mê làm một cái gì đấy và giảng dạy.
through this course.
thông qua khóa học này.